SUMMARY

6.04 years of experience into Finance majorly into end-to-end account controlling, managing multiple accounts within portfolio majorly from Financial Services which includes Banking and Insurance and some accounts from other sectors like that of CPRD, EUC and MALS, etc.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Awarded rising star during beginning of my career in Cappemini India Q4 2017
- Awarded in the most promising talent category during Finance Kick-off by our onshore leadership for my work on one of the crucial accounts during FY 2022.
- Certified for completing the program in 2022 for Young Emerging Professionals Ahead covering the following topics in Harvard Manage Mentor for Team creation, Presentation skills and Decision Making, etc.

EXPERIENCE

- Total Experience is of 6.3 years in Capgemini India as an- Account Controller (Grade- C1, portfolio handled-48.5 ME)
 Since May 2017 till date
- Currently working as an Account Controller and single handedly managing a portfolio of multiple accounts (majorly accounts from financial services) which includes accounts from our top 10 accounts with set of other small accounts in the currently managed portfolio of 48.5 million euros individually.
- Working as a real business partner with a clear operational mindset.
- Managing the work-relationship with multiple stakeholders involved (Accounts
 executives, Service delivery managers) and developing a good interface with the
 different Business units involved in delivering the contracts.
- Reporting and analyzing the main KPIs (P&L, Cash DOR, COR, ADRC...etc.) related to each account.
- End to End responsibility of the budget and forecast process, supported by our business counterparts, helping them to gain good predictability of the forecasts by reviewing the accounts health monthly.
- Monthly closing, preparing financial models to analyze results & explain
 variance and presenting it to Service Delivery Manager of Account, Market unit
 leadership and Finance General Management to explain the accounts financials
 during M Reviews and Account specific review with leadership.
- Pay special attention to the monthly cut off: a relevant revenue recognition process, expenses, explain variance analysis based on the actuals impact.
- Interfacing with the Delivery controlling team: onshore and offshore & challenge
 the Delivery costs containments and controls to review expense management,
 including the control of the productivity costs committed by the Delivery
 centers on the accounts.
- Responsible for reviewing and updating the reporting tools like that of E-monitoring. Control over WIP/BIA position and billing to client.
- Cash management and proposing actions to optimize DOR.
- Supporting business partner to coordinate with the Sales / Analyst team to submit new offers to the clients. Participate in the construction of deals and presales of your perimeter in close collaboration with the sales.
- Ensure compliance with internal and external audit.
- Explaining financials by reviewing and using various source like that of GFS, BO Reporting, ADMT, MS Excel & Power point and preparing Ad hoc reports to analyze and explain the same.
- Ensure the financial health of the projects & doing risk analysis monthly.
- Ensure compliance with Group Financial standards.

> <u>Summer Internship</u>

• Summer Internship done on Ground and Rooftop Solar projects in India at SBI CAPITAL INVESTMENT for 2 months (May 2021 -Jun 2021) done during my academic year FY2021 of Master's in Management Studies.

MAHESHWARI PATIL

Senior Consultant

Personal Details:

Contact no: 8879144991

Email ID:

maheshwariatwork@gmail.com

Located in: Mumbai, India

> Technical Skills:

FP & A

Financial reporting

Budgeting

Forecasting

Monthly variance analysis

DOR analysis

Cash collection management

AR /accounts receivable management

End to end controlling experience for North America region.

Soft Skills :

Fluent in English

Team building

Problem solving attitude

Multi Stake holder management

Proactive and believes in detailed analysis of work done

EDUCATION DETAILS:-

Masters in Management Studies in Finance

from University of Mumbai

(2015-2017)